[{"answer": "Put your hands up, and no one will get hurt.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Oh, my god, do you think it's him?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "It seems that at least from some of the people we have spoken to around here that both brothers occasionally spent time at this very apartment behind me.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "What has come out so far?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Piers, they all looked a little bit nervous when they were brought in.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What was the demeanor of these three suspects, would you say?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I think that's right.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, it just shows the nature of their relationship.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Why is that so significant?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Police investigations, criminal investigations, a long road of speculation interrupted by moments of clarification.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Is there enough in totality, do you think, to suggest a wider conspiracy in the Boston marathon bombings?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Well, in terms of this particular case, I think it's being handled very well.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "But what is your view about where the balance should be struck between an individual's right to civil liberty and between the right to go after terrorists and catch them?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Well, I think calling them three kids who tried to help a friend trivializes it a bit.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Or is there something a lot more sinister going on?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Well, they don't necessarily have to have been specialists themselves.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "So you have to imagine that they knew that the Vaseline was potentially a key piece of evidence, and that takes them away, I am sure, everyone would think this, from being the kids, the teenagers trying to help friends, into a much more serious situation, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "I don't know whether it's likely or not.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Is it likely they have got it, do you think?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "They sure are.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "What is your reading of it from an FBI point of view?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "It is pretty damning.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "I mean, you piece all that together, it's pretty damning, isn't it?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Yes, (EXPLETIVE DELETED) you.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Who, me?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "So, I'm not a radical --", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Have you read your (EXPLETIVE DELETED) jihad?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Well, because I'm a Muslim.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Why do you think he did this?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Really I feel really angry and frustration.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "As a Muslim, as a proud American as well, how do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Actually, that's the way I handle -- as we said, I'm well- trained physically and tough-trained.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Were you not tempted to hit him back and deal with him properly?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Doing well.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Ben, how are you?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I'm not surprised by this, because I think after Oklahoma City, we didn't know exactly how to use technology to our advantage to fight terrorists around the world.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "No, I see that as criminal profiling.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Would you see that as a new infringement on your civil liberties?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I didn't -- well, I didn't advocate for a background check, Piers, on fireworks.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "What is the difference?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "How many -- well, I will say this.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What is the difference between that scenario and somebody being suspicious buying fireworks?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Piers, 170 adults last month ran over children because they didn't look in their rear-view mirror.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "-- indiscriminately before people wake up and go that's enough kids shooting guns and being shot with guns, isn't it?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Piers, one of the things about coming up with a theory this early in an investigation is that it's probably going to be wrong.", "docId": "130501pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "What is your theory about what would have caused a 747 to go into this extraordinary rapid plunge like this?", "qSentId": 502}]